# Omar Ali Mohamed Frontend React.js

≥ omaralimohamedomar1@gmail.com

01286494837

Exemption from military service

https://omaraliomar.netlify.app/

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/omar-ali-9a4076267/

https://github.com/OmarAliBlack4

Bē https://omaraliomar.netlify.app/pages/portfolio

## **Profile**

Hi, I'm Omar, and I am currently a student at the Faculty of Business, at Alexandria University. I previously worked as an Assistant Manager at the Virginia Hotel for 3 years. Afterward, I joined a company called Copy and Print, where I was responsible for fixing Xerox photocopier machines. During this time, I developed a passion for programming and learned front-end. I am very enthusiastic about programming and continuously strive to expand my knowledge and skills in this field.

## Education

## Bachelor's degree

Faculty of Business Alexandria university undergraduate 2023 - 2024.

## **Professional Experience**

2019 - 2021	Photocopier Engineer
Alex, Egypt	Alfa Copy - Copy print

I worked as a Photocopier Engineer at Alfa copy company in 2019.

2017 – 2019 Hotel manager assistant

Matrouh, Egypt Virginia Hotel

I worked as an assistant manager in Matrouh for a period of 3 years.

Command Line

## **Skills**

HTML CSS

JS BOOTSTRAB
SASS GIT GITHUB

Computer Skills CS50

ICDL Photographer & Editing

## **Projects**

REACT IS

## **Movies Website**

Skills: html - css -js - react - redux - bootstrap - axios - real api.

 $https://movies-react-project-app.net lify.app/ \ \boxdot : host \\ https://github.com/OmarAliBlack4/movies-app \ \boxdot : code$ 

## **Cart App**

Skills: html - css -js - react - redux tool kit - bootstrap - axios - real api .

https://simple-cart-react.netlify.app/ ☑: host

https://github.com/OmarAliBlack4/cart-app ♂:code